<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Persian on Edible Reveries</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/persian/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Persian on Edible Reveries</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/persian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Baghli Poloh</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/baghli-poloh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/baghli-poloh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/bowl-of-baghli-poloh.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bowl-of-baghli-poloh.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This blog post brought to you by U.S., D.L., and M.B. Thanks for a great three years!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After a long hiatus, here I am again &amp;ndash; on a new computer, in a new house, in a new city, with a new husband. I also got&#xA;a new job and bangs. It&amp;rsquo;s been a crazy year my friends. With all that going on, who has the time to blog? So I let it&#xA;slide for longer and longer, let my blog sit in its own corner of the internet, sad and lonely.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tachin - Layered Persian Rice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tachin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tachin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/tachin/saffron-yogurt.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;saffron-yogurt.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Saffron lemon yogurt mixture&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This, in my mind, is the ultimate in comfort food. I crave this dish at all times. If given the opportunity I will&#xA;shamelessly eat the entire pan. It’s also a showstopper at dinner parties and a great “entry level” Persian dish.&#xA;Everyone likes tachin once they try it; it’s exotic, but the flavors are just close enough to home that they are still&#xA;accessible to less-adventurous palates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Year, Persian Style</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/persian-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/persian-new-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/persian-new-year/norouz-dinner.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;norouz-dinner.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Norouz dinner&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My family’s Persian new year celebrations are some of my favorite memories from childhood (besides Thanksgiving &amp;ndash;&#xA;nothing trumps Thanksgiving). Honestly, I love any holiday that is drawn out for days on end, and Norouz always seems&#xA;like it lasts for weeks, probably because of the surrounding holidays.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Right before the new year, Iranians celebrate Chaharshanbe Suri, which Wikipedia is telling me literally translates to&#xA;Wednesday Red. Chaharshanbe Suri is a fire festival &amp;ndash; on the evening of the last Tuesday before the new year, Iranians&#xA;light bonfires and jump over them. This is supposed to be a purification rite. The fire is meant to burn away all of&#xA;your sickness and problems, leaving only warmth in its wake. My family would always have a huge party, the kind of party&#xA;that everyone in our lives was invited to (including teachers and principals - seeing them out of context was always&#xA;equal parts fascinating and horrifying to me, but it did give me some bragging rights on the playground). My mother&#xA;would go all out cooking for these parties. I remember standing in the kitchen with her for hours, rolling dolmas and&#xA;frying zulbia (syrupy Persian fritters) together. I loved the ritual and care appetizers took, it was so different from&#xA;the rote cooking of our daily lives. It felt special. My favorite part of the night was always when we would jump over&#xA;the fire. When I was very young, my father always helped swing me over the fire mid-jump, to make sure I didn’t fall&#xA;in - I was a very cautious child. My parents must have snapped dozens of photos of those jumps, and every year my&#xA;sisters and I have such a look of excitement on our faces - how daring we felt!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aashe Jo (Persian Chicken &amp; Barley Soup)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/aashe-jo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/aashe-jo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/aashe-jo/cut-veggies.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;cut-veggies.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This week was Persian New Year - Salleh no mobarak! (which is “Happy new year” in Farsi!)  I’m celebrating this weekend&#xA;with the family - I’ll post pictures of the food and decorations next week. It’s a big party not to be missed!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I grew up in a mixed household &amp;ndash; half Iranian, and half American. I’m a true mutt. As a result, my idea of comfort food&#xA;sometimes differs from my peers. Though I’ll go to town on mac and cheese with the best of them, I also regularly crave&#xA;feta with walnuts for breakfast and complicated layered rice dishes for dinner. I generally only get to indulge when I&#xA;visit my family. Most Persian recipes have imported ingredients I have to go out of my way for. This lazy home cook&#xA;hates making extra grocery trips, so I just&amp;hellip;wait for my mom to cook for me. Usually.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
