<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fall on Edible Reveries</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/fall/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fall on Edible Reveries</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/fall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Butternut Squash Minestrone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/butternut-squash-minestrone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/butternut-squash-minestrone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/butternut-squash-minestrone.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;butternut-squash-minestrone.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think every fall I adopt a favorite soup recipe and make it over and over until it’s perfect and everyone else is tired of it.  I’ve been making this soup practically weekly since it started getting cold and I’m certainly not bored yet.  It’s a crowd pleaser, what my inlaws call “friendly food” – warming and hearty.  It’s so loaded with vegetables that it’s also very healthy without sacrificing any flavor.  A pot of this soup is enough to feed me lunch all week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whole Wheat Apple Muffins</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whole-wheat-apple-muffins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whole-wheat-apple-muffins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/apple-muffins.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;apple-muffins.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Whole wheat apple muffins - they look unassuming, but they taste so good&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think I may have mentioned recently how much I love fall. Well, fall and baking go together like you wouldn’t believe!&#xA;Ever since the air started getting crisper, I’ve been baking every weekend and an alarming number of weekdays. As a&#xA;rule, I don’t love baking as much as I love cooking, mostly because I’m terrifically lazy. Baking requires precision&#xA;measurements and exact times. I prefer throwing things together and letting them stew for hours. But it’s fall and my&#xA;kitchen is cold so I need a hot oven and warm spices to keep me toasty!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall Brings Love</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fall-brings-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fall-brings-love/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/fig-challah.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;fig-challah.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fig &amp;amp; olive oil challah&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I woke up this weekend and turned my face to look out my bedroom window. It’s finally fall.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I love fall. I love that I get to wear sweaters and jackets during fall. I love that my hair whips around in the wind&#xA;during fall. I love that when I wrap a scarf around my neck, it keeps getting pushed farther by the fall wind, until my&#xA;face is finally obscured and I can’t see where I’m going. The fall chill has a vitality to it that isn’t the same in the&#xA;winter. It’s crisper - I feel like I can hear it and feel it around me. Or is it just the crunching leaves that I can&#xA;hear? Fall is alive and it makes me feel alive too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
