<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lunch on Edible Reveries</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/lunch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lunch on Edible Reveries</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/lunch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thai Tofu Rice Bowl</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/thai-tofu-rice-bowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/thai-tofu-rice-bowl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;thai-tofu-rice-bowl&#34;&gt;Thai Tofu Rice Bowl&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;dressing adapted from Everyday Maven&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dressing:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1/2 cup water&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1/8 cup fish sauce&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1/8 cup rice vinegar&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Juice from 1/2 a lime&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3 tablespoons sugar&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1 clove garlic, minced&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1/2 teaspoon chili pepper flakes&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quick Pickled Carrots:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shredded carrots&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1 tablespoon sugar&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1 teaspoon salt&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enough rice wine vinegar and water to cover in equal amounts&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rice Bowl:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Brown rice&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Baked tofu&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cilantro, torn&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Basil, torn&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Butternut Squash Minestrone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/butternut-squash-minestrone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/butternut-squash-minestrone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/butternut-squash-minestrone.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;butternut-squash-minestrone.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think every fall I adopt a favorite soup recipe and make it over and over until it’s perfect and everyone else is tired of it.  I’ve been making this soup practically weekly since it started getting cold and I’m certainly not bored yet.  It’s a crowd pleaser, what my inlaws call “friendly food” – warming and hearty.  It’s so loaded with vegetables that it’s also very healthy without sacrificing any flavor.  A pot of this soup is enough to feed me lunch all week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thai Basil Turkey Meatball Spring Rolls</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/thai-basil-meatball-springroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/thai-basil-meatball-springroll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/thai-basil-meatball-springroll/springroll.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;springroll.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thai basil turkey meatball spring rolls&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do you ever try a recipe that sounds delicious and end up totally disappointed? Not that the finished product is bad,&#xA;it’s just … underwhelming. This is doubly unfortunate if you are testing said new recipe on a dinner guest (I almost&#xA;always use my dinner guests as guinea pigs. As of the publishing of this article, none have ever complained about this&#xA;practice). Last night I had a friend over for dinner and had just that experience. I made Thai basil turkey meatballs&#xA;with a spicy garlic dipping sauce and … we were less than impressed. They were edible, and we weren’t hungry anymore&#xA;afterwards, but I wasn’t really looking forward to finishing them up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aashe Jo (Persian Chicken &amp; Barley Soup)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/aashe-jo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/aashe-jo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/aashe-jo/cut-veggies.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;cut-veggies.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This week was Persian New Year - Salleh no mobarak! (which is “Happy new year” in Farsi!)  I’m celebrating this weekend&#xA;with the family - I’ll post pictures of the food and decorations next week. It’s a big party not to be missed!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I grew up in a mixed household &amp;ndash; half Iranian, and half American. I’m a true mutt. As a result, my idea of comfort food&#xA;sometimes differs from my peers. Though I’ll go to town on mac and cheese with the best of them, I also regularly crave&#xA;feta with walnuts for breakfast and complicated layered rice dishes for dinner. I generally only get to indulge when I&#xA;visit my family. Most Persian recipes have imported ingredients I have to go out of my way for. This lazy home cook&#xA;hates making extra grocery trips, so I just&amp;hellip;wait for my mom to cook for me. Usually.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lentil Soup: The Basics and My Favorite</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lentil-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lentil-soup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/lentil-soup/soup.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soup.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m a huge fan of adaptable pantry recipes - meals that allow me to make as few trips to the grocery store as possible&#xA;and just cook according to what I have on hand. Lentil soup is a great one for this, as you can make it with whatever is&#xA;in your fridge and it will still taste warming and hearty, as well as unutterably delicious (this is doubly true if you&#xA;make a batch of &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts/biscuit-quest&#34;&gt;warm biscuits&lt;/a&gt; or cornbread to eat alongside the soup!)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
