<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Soup on Edible Reveries</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/soup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Soup on Edible Reveries</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/soup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Butternut Squash Minestrone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/butternut-squash-minestrone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/butternut-squash-minestrone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/butternut-squash-minestrone.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;butternut-squash-minestrone.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think every fall I adopt a favorite soup recipe and make it over and over until it’s perfect and everyone else is tired of it.  I’ve been making this soup practically weekly since it started getting cold and I’m certainly not bored yet.  It’s a crowd pleaser, what my inlaws call “friendly food” – warming and hearty.  It’s so loaded with vegetables that it’s also very healthy without sacrificing any flavor.  A pot of this soup is enough to feed me lunch all week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aashe Jo (Persian Chicken &amp; Barley Soup)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/aashe-jo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/aashe-jo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/aashe-jo/cut-veggies.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;cut-veggies.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This week was Persian New Year - Salleh no mobarak! (which is “Happy new year” in Farsi!)  I’m celebrating this weekend&#xA;with the family - I’ll post pictures of the food and decorations next week. It’s a big party not to be missed!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I grew up in a mixed household &amp;ndash; half Iranian, and half American. I’m a true mutt. As a result, my idea of comfort food&#xA;sometimes differs from my peers. Though I’ll go to town on mac and cheese with the best of them, I also regularly crave&#xA;feta with walnuts for breakfast and complicated layered rice dishes for dinner. I generally only get to indulge when I&#xA;visit my family. Most Persian recipes have imported ingredients I have to go out of my way for. This lazy home cook&#xA;hates making extra grocery trips, so I just&amp;hellip;wait for my mom to cook for me. Usually.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
