<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Family on Edible Reveries</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Family on Edible Reveries</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fall Brings Love</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/baked-turkey-meatballs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/baked-turkey-meatballs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/fig-challah.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;fig-challah.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fig &amp;amp; olive oil challah&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I woke up this weekend and turned my face to look out my bedroom window. It’s finally fall.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I love fall. I love that I get to wear sweaters and jackets during fall. I love that my hair whips around in the wind&#xA;during fall. I love that when I wrap a scarf around my neck, it keeps getting pushed farther by the fall wind, until my&#xA;face is finally obscured and I can’t see where I’m going. The fall chill has a vitality to it that isn’t the same in the&#xA;winter. It’s crisper - I feel like I can hear it and feel it around me. Or is it just the crunching leaves that I can&#xA;hear? Fall is alive and it makes me feel alive too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall Brings Love</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fall-brings-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fall-brings-love/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/fig-challah.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;fig-challah.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fig &amp;amp; olive oil challah&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I woke up this weekend and turned my face to look out my bedroom window. It’s finally fall.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I love fall. I love that I get to wear sweaters and jackets during fall. I love that my hair whips around in the wind&#xA;during fall. I love that when I wrap a scarf around my neck, it keeps getting pushed farther by the fall wind, until my&#xA;face is finally obscured and I can’t see where I’m going. The fall chill has a vitality to it that isn’t the same in the&#xA;winter. It’s crisper - I feel like I can hear it and feel it around me. Or is it just the crunching leaves that I can&#xA;hear? Fall is alive and it makes me feel alive too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May Birthday Family Feast!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/may-birthday-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/may-birthday-feast/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/may-birthday-feast/summer-veggies.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;summer-veggies.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Summer vegetables ready to be grilled&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;May is a big month in my family &amp;ndash; we have 3 birthdays to celebrate, plus mother’s day. Since we all have busy schedules&#xA;and I don’t live in the same city as everyone else, we have started celebrating all of the holidays during one big&#xA;weekend bash. And if you’ve learned anything about me by now you should know &amp;ndash; my family celebrates with food!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Failure Strikes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/when-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/when-failure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, life just doesn’t work out the way you want it to.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/when-failure/happy-birthday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;happy-birthday.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lemon lime layer cake with whipped cream frosting&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Take last weekend for instance. It was Friday night and I was so excited for the weekend to come. It was my sister’s&#xA;birthday AND my grandfather’s birthday, so the whole family was getting together to celebrate and I was in charge of the&#xA;cake. I found out I was in charge of the cake when my sister texted me a recipe link and the words “My Birthday”.&#xA;Nothing else. We communicate so easily in my family.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Year, Persian Style</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/persian-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/persian-new-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/persian-new-year/norouz-dinner.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;norouz-dinner.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Norouz dinner&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My family’s Persian new year celebrations are some of my favorite memories from childhood (besides Thanksgiving &amp;ndash;&#xA;nothing trumps Thanksgiving). Honestly, I love any holiday that is drawn out for days on end, and Norouz always seems&#xA;like it lasts for weeks, probably because of the surrounding holidays.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Right before the new year, Iranians celebrate Chaharshanbe Suri, which Wikipedia is telling me literally translates to&#xA;Wednesday Red. Chaharshanbe Suri is a fire festival &amp;ndash; on the evening of the last Tuesday before the new year, Iranians&#xA;light bonfires and jump over them. This is supposed to be a purification rite. The fire is meant to burn away all of&#xA;your sickness and problems, leaving only warmth in its wake. My family would always have a huge party, the kind of party&#xA;that everyone in our lives was invited to (including teachers and principals - seeing them out of context was always&#xA;equal parts fascinating and horrifying to me, but it did give me some bragging rights on the playground). My mother&#xA;would go all out cooking for these parties. I remember standing in the kitchen with her for hours, rolling dolmas and&#xA;frying zulbia (syrupy Persian fritters) together. I loved the ritual and care appetizers took, it was so different from&#xA;the rote cooking of our daily lives. It felt special. My favorite part of the night was always when we would jump over&#xA;the fire. When I was very young, my father always helped swing me over the fire mid-jump, to make sure I didn’t fall&#xA;in - I was a very cautious child. My parents must have snapped dozens of photos of those jumps, and every year my&#xA;sisters and I have such a look of excitement on our faces - how daring we felt!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
