<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dessert on Edible Reveries</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/dessert/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dessert on Edible Reveries</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/dessert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Whole Wheat Apple Muffins</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whole-wheat-apple-muffins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whole-wheat-apple-muffins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/apple-muffins.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;apple-muffins.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Whole wheat apple muffins - they look unassuming, but they taste so good&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think I may have mentioned recently how much I love fall. Well, fall and baking go together like you wouldn’t believe!&#xA;Ever since the air started getting crisper, I’ve been baking every weekend and an alarming number of weekdays. As a&#xA;rule, I don’t love baking as much as I love cooking, mostly because I’m terrifically lazy. Baking requires precision&#xA;measurements and exact times. I prefer throwing things together and letting them stew for hours. But it’s fall and my&#xA;kitchen is cold so I need a hot oven and warm spices to keep me toasty!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhubarb Strawberry Crumble</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/rhubarb-strawberry-crumble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/rhubarb-strawberry-crumble/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/rhubarb-strawberry-crumble/crumble.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;crumble.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rhubarb Strawberry Crumble&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don’t think I’ve mentioned it on here yet, but I get a biweekly CSA box delivered to my home. CSA boxes definitely&#xA;aren’t for everyone (I used to waste a shameful amount of produce when I was younger and received one) but they are&#xA;great for my cooking now. I end up with produce I never would have bought otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rhubarb is in that category, but I’m really not sure why. I like rhubarb, I grew up eating wonderful strawberry rhubarb&#xA;pies that my mother and grandmother made. My sister is crazy for the stuff. It definitely has a presence in my life &amp;ndash;&#xA;but not on my shopping list. I have never, ever gone out of my way to buy rhubarb. I’ve just ended up with it, either as&#xA;a gift or in my CSA box. And thank goodness for that!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lemon Lime Layer Cake with Whipped Cream Frosting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lemon-lime-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lemon-lime-cake/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On the heels of last week’s delicious disaster, here is the recipe for Lemon Lime Layer Cake with Lemon Whipped Cream&#xA;Frosting and Raspberry Filling. This cake is springy (texturally speaking, but it also suits the warm weather) and&#xA;flavorful - the lemon makes it taste lighter than all that whipped cream should make you feel. Raspberry is meant to be&#xA;paired with lemon!  I served this alongside fresh strawberries and ended up dipping the berries in the whipped cream (&#xA;another match made in heaven!)  If you are fancier than me, try decorating the cake with fresh berries on top of the&#xA;cream.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Failure Strikes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/when-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/when-failure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, life just doesn’t work out the way you want it to.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/when-failure/happy-birthday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;happy-birthday.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lemon lime layer cake with whipped cream frosting&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Take last weekend for instance. It was Friday night and I was so excited for the weekend to come. It was my sister’s&#xA;birthday AND my grandfather’s birthday, so the whole family was getting together to celebrate and I was in charge of the&#xA;cake. I found out I was in charge of the cake when my sister texted me a recipe link and the words “My Birthday”.&#xA;Nothing else. We communicate so easily in my family.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
